Finding Aid for Penn Central Transportation Company Records 1835-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- New York Central Railroad Company, 1835-1981; 116 linear feet
  - New York Central Railroad Company: Subsidiaries
    - Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad Company
      - Operating Statements, 1911-1913 (Volume 1)
        (oversize volumes 16 and 17)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1951-1960, 10 items (Box 108)
        - 1973-1975, 3 items (Box 283)
    - Indiana Harbor Connecting Railroad Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1923-1931 (scattered) (Box 109)
    - Indiana, Illinois, and Iowa Railroad Company
      - Articles of Consolidation and Miscellaneous
        - 1881-1882, 1894; 1905 (Box 109)
        - 1898, 1905 (Box 109)
      - Cremation of Bonds Certificates, 1900-1901 (Box 109)
      - Mortgages
        - 1882-1898 (scattered) (Box 109)
        - 1893-1895, 1898 (Box 109)
        - 1898-1902 (Box 109)
    - Indiana, Illinois and Iowa Railroad Company (Illinois)
      - Articles of Organization and Miscellaneous, 1881; 1905 (Box 109)
      - Minutes, 1881-1902 (Volume 18)
    - Indiana, Illinois and Iowa Railroad Company (Indiana)
      - Articles of Association and Miscellaneous, 1881; 1892-1923 (scattered) (Box 109)
    - Indiana, Illinois and Iowa Railroad Company (Iowa)
      - Articles of Incorporation (certified 1892), 1881 (Box 109)
    - Indiana, Illinois and Iowa Railway Company (Indiana)
      - Articles of Association and Miscellaneous, 1892-1893; 1905 (Box 109)
      - Minutes, 1893-1898 (Volume 19)
    - Indiana Northern Railway Company
      - Minutes, 1890-1897; 1 volumes (Box 109)
      - Stock Subscription Book, 1881; 1 volumes (Box 109)
    - Jackson Coal Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1883-1909; 1 volumes (Box 109)
      - Mortgage, 1884-1913 (scattered) (Box 109)
    - Jackson, Lansing and Saginaw Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Amendments 1864-1867, 1871-1872 (certified 1919) (Box 109)
      - Minutes, 1864-1916 (Volume 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1871-1931 (scattered) (Box 109)
      - Mortgage and Correspondence, 1865; 1885-1887; 1899; 1931 (Box 109)
    - Jamestown and Franklin Railroad Company
      - Contract and Agreement of Merger and Consolidation, 1871 (Box 110)
      - Minutes: Board of Directors
        - 1862-1864 (Volume 21)
        - 1862-1889, 1 volumes (Box 110)
        - 1890-1909, 1 volumes (Box 110)
      - Minutes: Executive Committee, 1863-1864; 1 volumes (Box 110)
      - Miscellaneous, 1910; 1916 (Box 110)
    - Jamestown, Franklin and Clearfield Railroad Company
      - Agreement of Consolidation and Merger, 1902; 1908-1913; 1943 (Box 110)
      - Minutes, 1909-1915; 1 volumes (Box 110)
    - Joliet and Northern Indiana Railroad Company
      - Articles of Consolidation, 1854 (Box 111)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1934-1935, 1938; 1941; 1944 (Box 111)
        - 1946, 1948-1949; 1952; 1954 (Box 111)
        - 1955-1960 (Box 111)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 284)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors, 1854-1942 (Volume 22)
        - 1943-1981 (Box 284)
          Minute book no. 2
        - Stockholders' Annual Meetings
          - 1906-1907, 1909 (Box 111)
          - 1913, 1916; 1918-1919 (Box 111)
          - 1920, 1922-1924 (Box 111)
          - 1925-1960, 9 folders (Box 111)
          - 1961-1967, 7 items (Box 284)
      - Miscellaneous, 1875; 1910; 1915-1917 (Box 111)
    - Junction Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1870 (Box 112)
        (See: Connection Railroad Company, Articles of Association, 1870)
      - Consolidation Agreement, 1853 (Box 112)
        (See: Cleveland and Toledo Railroad Company, Consolidation Agreement, 1853.)
      - Consolidations and Mergers, 1870-1871 (Box 112)
      - Incorporation Act, 1846 (Box 112)
      - Minutes
        - 1850-1853, 1 volumes (Box 112)
        - 1870-1871 (Box 112)
    - Junction Railway Company
      - Articles of Association, 1872; 1894 (Box 112)
    - Kalamazoo, Allegan and Grand Rapids Railroad Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1868-1869; 1918-1919; 1920 (Box 112)
      - Title Papers, 1867-1919 (Box 112)
        in document box
    - Kalamazoo and Allegan Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1925), 1867 (Box 112)
      - Minute book
        - 1868-1971 (Box 284)
      - Wavers of noise volume (Box 284)
      - Notice of special meeting of stockholders, 1982 (Box 284)
    - Kalamazoo and Grand Rapids Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1925), 1868 (Box 112)
    - Kalamazoo and Schoolcraft Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1866 (Box 112)
      - Minutes, 1866-1869 (Box 112)
        (See: Kalamazoo and White Pigeon Railroad Company, Minutes, 1869-1914)
    - Kalamazoo and South Haven Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1869-1916; 1 volumes (Box 113)
      - Miscellaneous, 1869-1941 (scattered) (Box 113)
    - Kalamazoo and White Pigeon Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1869-1914; 1 volumes (Box 113)
      - Miscellaneous, 1869-1940 (scattered) (Box 113)
    - Kanawha and Michigan Railway Company
      - Annual Reports, 1910-1918 (Box 114)
    - Kankakee Stock Yards Company
      - Minutes, October 1898 (Box 114)
    - LaGrange Connecting Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1927-1932; 1 volumes (Box 114)
    - Lake Erie, Alliance and Wheeling Coal Company
      - Minutes, 1901-1909 (Box 114)
    - Lake Erie, Alliance and Wheeling Railroad Company
      - Agreement of Merger, 1941-1952 (Box 114)
      - Annual Reports, 1910-1912 (Box 114)
      - Board Docket, 1933-1952 (scattered) (Box 115)
      - Minutes
        - 1901-June 1912 (Box 115)
        - October 1912-1952, 1 volumes (Box 115)
      - Satisfaction of Mortgage, 1903-1904; 1908 (Box 115)
    - Lake Erie and Eastern Railroad Company
      - Board Docket, 1947 (Box 115)
    - Lake Erie and Pittsburgh Railway Company
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1903 (Box 116)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1920, 1922; 1931; 1933-1935 (Box 116)
        - 1936-1939 (Box 116)
        - 1940, 1942-1944 (Box 116)
        - 1945-1960, 4 folders (Box 116)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 285)
      - Minutes
        - April 1903-March 1908 (Box 268)
        - April 1908-March 1928, 1 volumes (Box 116)
        - April 1928-December 1952, 1 volumes (Box 116)
        - (no. 4), 1953-1970 (Box 285)
      - Mortgages
        - 1911-1917 (Box 117)
        - 1915-1965, 2 folders (Box 117)
      - Operating Statements
        - 1911-1912 (Volume 73)
        - 1915 (Volume 74)
        - 1916 (Volume 75)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission, 1921; 1951-1960; 11 items (Box 117)
    - Lake Erie and Western Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports, 1910-1919 (Box 117)
      - Board Dockets, 1918-1922 (Box 117)
    - Lake Shore and Michigan Southern Railway Company
      - Agreement of Merger and Consolidation (certified 1905), 1869 (Box 118)
      - Articles of Consolidation and Miscellaneous, 1853; 1869; 1872; 1874; 1966 (Box 118)
      - Annual Reports, 1866-1914; 4 volumes (Box 118)
      - Contracts, 1906-1907 (Box 118)
      - Correspondence, 1903; 1908 (Box 118)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors and Executive Committee
          - June 1869-November 1886 (Volume 24)
          - May 1877-April 1887 (Volume 25)
          - May 1877-March 1898 (Volume 26)
          - May 1898-December 1906 (Volume 27)
          - January 1907-December 1910, 1 volumes (Box 119)
          - January 1911-December 1914, 1 volumes (Box 119)
        - Executive Committee, November 12, 1869 (Box 120)
        - Executive and Finance Committees, 1886-1900 (Volume 48)
        - Finance Committee, October 1869-February 1870; 1 volumes (Box 120)
      - Miscellaneous, 1869; 1906-1907 (Box 120)
      - Mortgages, 1897; 1914-1915 (Box 120)
      - Stock Exchange, Applications to, 1904-1911 (Box 120)
    - Lake Shore, Chicago and Wabash Railway Company
      - Agreement of Consolidation, 1869 (Box 120)
    - Lake Shore Railway Company
      - Articles of Consolidation and Correspondence, 1869; 1966 (Box 120)
      - Dividend Record, 1868-1869 (Box 120)
        (See: Cleveland, Painesville and Ashtabula Railroad Company, Dividend Record, 1868-1869.)
      - Minutes, December 1868-May 1869. (Box 120)
        (See: Cleveland, Painesville, and Ashtabula Railroad Company, Minutes, August 1862-June 1868.)
    - Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Company
      - Minutes: Board of Directors and Stockholders, 1946-1962; 1 volumes (Box 120)
      - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
        - 1949-1960, 12 items (Box 120)
        - 1973-1974, 2 items (Box 285)
    - Lansing and Jackson Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1864 (Box 120)
        (See: Jackson, Lansing and Saginaw Railroad Company, Minutes, 1865-1916)
    - Lansing Manufacturers' Railroad
      - Board Dockets
        - 1934, 1938; 1940; 1944; 1947; 1949; 1952 (Box 121)
        - 1954-1958, 1960 (Box 121)
        - 1961-1967 (Box 285)
      - Minutes
        - 1904-1927, 1 volumes (Box 121)
        - 1928-1969 (Box 285)
      - Miscellaneous, 1905; 1907; 1920; 1930 (Box 121)
    - Lansing Transit Railway Company
      - Board Dockets
        - 1934, 1938; 1944; 1949; 1952; 1954; 1957; 1958; 1960 (Box 121)
        - 1963-1966 (Box 285)
      - Minute books
        - 1886-1921 (Box 121)
      - 1922-1969 (Box 285)
    - Mackinac Transportation Company (Box 121)
      (See: Pennsylvania Railroad Company: Subsidiaries, Mackinac Transportation Company)
    - Mahoning and Shenango Valley Railway Company
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1886 (Box 121)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1934, 1942; 1944; 1946; 1949 (Box 121)
        - 1952, 1954-1955; 1957-1960 (Box 121)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 285)
      - Minutes
        - October 1886-May 1911, 1 volumes (Box 121)
        - May 1912-May 1956, 1 volumes (Box 121)
        - 1957-1981 (Box 285)
          minute book no. 3
    - Mahoning Coal Railroad Company
      - Accounts, 1912 (Box 121)
      - Agreement (with Lake Shore and Michigan Southern Railroad Company), 1873 (Box 121)
      - Agreements and Certificates re Branch Lines, 1900-1914 (scattered) (Box 121)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1905-1960, 3 folders (Box 121)
        - 1961-1974 (Box 286)
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence, 1871; 1913 (Box 121)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1931-1960, 9 folders (Box 121)
        - 1961-1967 (Box 286)
      - Board Meetings: Secretary's Files, 1914-1918 (Box 122)
      - Certificate of Incorporation and Supplemental certificates, 1871-1873 (Box 122)
      - Contracts, 1889; 1902 (Box 122)
      - Correspondence
        - File 3013-1/2, 1900; 1906-1912 (Box 122)
        - File 4043-15
          - 1907-1912 (Box 122)
          - 1913-1916 (Box 122)
          - 1914-1918 (Box 122)
          - 1917-1918 (Box 122)
      - Financial Records-miscellaneous, 1892-1895; 1903-1912; 2 folders (Box 122)
      - Income Accounts and General Balance Sheet, 1914-1918 (Box 122)
      - Minutes
        - 1871-1906 (Box 122)
        - 1907-March 1929, 1 volumes (Box 123)
        - May 1, 1929-September 13, 1950 (Box 60, Reel 39)
        - May 1929-1948, 1 volumes (Box 123)
        - 1948-1964 (Box 286)
          minute book no. 4
        - December 3, 1964-December 7, 1981, 1 volumes (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 124)
      - Monthly Report of Expenditures, 1900-1923 (Box 124)
      - Mortgage, 1884-1941 (Box 124)
      - Organization Expenses, 1910-1917 (Box 124)
      - Secretary's Correspondence, 1884-1957 (scattered) (Box 124)
      - Stock Records, 1872 (Box 124)
      - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1903; 1907 (Box 124)
    - Mahoning State Line Railroad Company
      - Board Dockets
        - 1934-1960 (scattered) (Box 124)
        - 1961-1967 (Box 286)
      - Minutes, August 8, 1891-January 8, 1951 (Box 60, Reel 39)
    - Michigan Air Line Railroad Company
      (See also: Air Line Railway of Michigan)
      - Articles of Consolidation, 1868 (Box 124)
      - Board Dockets
        - 1944, 1949; 1952; 1954-1955; 1957; 1959-1960 (Box 124)
        - 1962-1966 (Box 286)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors
          - 1868-1939 (Box 124)
          - 1944-1976 (Box 286)
            minute book no. 2
          - (meetings held in Chicago), January 1870-June 1871 (Box 124)
        - Executive Committee, 1870-1877 (Box 124)
        - Stockholders' Annual Meetings
          - 1914, 1916 (Box 124)
          - 1922, 1924 (Box 124)
          - 1926, 1928 (Box 124)
          - 1930, 1932; 1939 (Box 124)
          - 1944, 1947 (Box 124)
          - 1951 (Box 124)
          - 1953-1954 (Box 124)
          - 1956-1957 (Box 124)
          - 1958-1960 (Box 124)
        - Stockholders' Annual Meetings
          - 1961-1967 (Box 286)
      - Miscellaneous, 1870; 1918-1923 (scattered) (Box 124)
      - Stockholders, List of
        - June 1868 (Box 125)
        - Undated (Box 125)
      - Stock Ledger
        - 1887-1934 (Box 125)
        - 1887-1948 (Box 125)
      - Stock Record Book, undated (Box 125)
    - Michigan and Mackinaw Railroad Company
      - Articles of Incorporation and Correspondence, 1891; 1919 (Box 125)
    - Michigan and Ohio Railroad Company
      - Articles of Consolidation, 1883 (Box 125)
      - Minutes, October 1883-June 1885; 1 volumes (Box 125, Reel 67)
        (also on microfilm reel no. 67 in Box 60)
    - Michigan Central Bridge Company
      - Minutes, December 19, 1895-August 15, 1905 (Box 60, Reel 67)
    - Michigan Central Railroad Company
      - Administrative Records
        - Annual Reports, 1847-1929; 9 items (Box 126)
        - Board of Directors
          - General
            - 1879, 1905 (Box 127)
            - 1909-1956 (scattered) (Box 127)
          - Committees, 1878-1941 (scattered) (Box 127)
          - Dockets
            - 1918 (Box 127)
            - January-July 1920 (Box 127)
            - September-December 1920 (Box 127)
            - 1921 (Box 127)
            - 1922 (Box 127)
            - 1931-1948, 17 folders (Box 127)
            - 1949-1960, 16 folders (Box 128)
            - 1961-1967, 4 folders (Box 287)
          - Minutes
            - March 1846-May 1858, 1 volumes (Box 129)
            - June 1858-June 1878, 1 volumes (Box 129)
            - June 1878-April 1888 (Volume 28)
            - May 1888-December 1900 (Volume 29)
            - April 1901-December 1907 (Volume 30)
            - January 1908-December 1913, 1 volumes (Box 130)
            - February 1914-April 1918, 1 volumes (Box 130)
            - May 1918-April 1922, 1 volumes (Box 131)
            - May 1922-May 5, 1926, 1 volumes (Box 131)
            - May 6, 1926-December 19, 1928, 1 volumes (Box 132)
            - January 3, 1929-February 20, 1935, 1 volumes (Box 132)
            - May 1935-December 1945, 1 volumes (Box 133)
            - 1946-1952 (Box 288)
              minute book no. 11
            - 1953-1959 (Box 288)
              minute book no. 12
            - 1959-1962 (Box 289)
              minute book no. 13
            - 1963-1974 (Box 289)
              minute book no. 14
            - May 1946-September 1952 (Box 133)
              photocopy
            - May 1953-May 1959 (Box 133)
        - Historical Material, 1869-1946 (scattered) (Box 133)
        - Historical Material, Newspaper Clippings, 1912; 1922; 1936 (Box 133)
        - Legal Records
          - Agreements, 1907 (Box 133)
          - Articles of Association and Amendments, 1901; 1955; 1957 (Box 133)
          - Contracts, 1906-1907 (Box 133)
          - Contracts and Deeds, 1849-1920 (scattered) (Box 133)
          - Leases, 1930; 1937; 1942 (Box 133)
          - Mortgages
            - 1857, 1883-1884 (Box 133)
            - 1872, 1883; 1920-1923 (Box 133)
            - 1912, 1917 (Box 133)
        - Secretary's Files
          - General Correspondence
            - 1881-1956 (scattered) (Box 133)
            - 1901-1930 (Box 133)
          - Correspondence with Stockholders, 1926-1928 (Box 133)
      - Financial Records
        - Auditor's Correspondence, 1912 (Box 133)
        - Income statements (miscellaneous) (Box 289)
        - Balance Sheets
          - 1888-1917 (Volume 31)
          - 1918-1921, 1 volumes (Box 135)
          - 1922-1923 (Box 135)
          - 1924-1925, 1 volumes (Box 135)
          - 1926-1927, 1 volumes (Box 136)
          - 1928-1930, 1 volumes (Box 136)
          - 1931-1934, 1 volumes (Box 136)
          - 1935-1938, 1 volumes (Box 137)
          - 1939-1944, 1 volumes (Box 137)
          - 1945-1951, 1 volumes (Box 137)
          - 1952-1956, 1 volumes (Box 137)
        - Journal, General
          - 1873-1904 (Volume 32)
          - 1875-1877 (Volume 33)
          - 1880 (Volume 34)
          - 1881-1882 (Volume 35)
        - Ledger, General
          - 1856-1872 (Box 268)
          - 1872-1905 (Volume 37)
          - 1873-1875 (Volume 38)
          - 1875-1877 (Volume 39)
          - 1876 (Volume 40)
          - 1877-1880 (Volume 41)
          - 1877-1881 (Volume 42)
          - 1881 (Volume 43)
          - 1881-1882 (Volume 44)
          - 1882 (Volume 45)
          - 1882 (Volume 46)
            (continued)
          - 1882-1890 (Volume 47)
        - Operating Statements, 1923; 1 volumes (Box 138)
        - Operations Statistics, Summary of
          - 1900, 1 volumes (Box 138)
          - 1901, 1 volumes (Box 138)
        - Reports to Interstate Commerce Commission
          - 1923, 1 items (Box 139)
          - 1927-1934, 8 items (Box 139)
        - Securities
          - General, 1880; 1890 (Box 139)
          - Applications to New York Stock Exchange
            - 1902-1904 (Box 139)
            - 1906, 1909; 1915; 1919; 1930; 1931 (Box 139)
          - Stock Transfer Correspondence, 1898 (Box 139)
        - Tax Assessments, Applications for Revision of, 1894-1902; 1904-1907 (Box 139)
        - Treasurers' Letterbooks
          - March 1850-April 1852, 1 volumes (Box 140)
          - April 1852-June 1854, 1 volumes (Box 140)
      - Pension Department
        - Employee Relations Correspondence, 1909-1910; 1950 (Box 140)
    - Michigan Midland and Canada Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1919), 1872-1874 (Box 140)
      - Journal, General, 1872-1941 (Box 268)
      - Ledger, General, 1875-1949 (Volume 49)
      - Minutes, September 11, 1872-June 14, 1905 (Box 60, Reel 67)
    - Michigan Midland Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1919), 1872 (Box 140)
    - Michigan Southern and Northern Indiana Railroad Company
      - Annual Reports
        - 1853, 1855; 1857-1863; 1 volumes (Box 140)
        - 1866-1869, 1 volumes (Box 140)
      - Articles of Consolidation, 1855 (Box 140)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors
          - April 1855-January 1865, 1 volumes (Box 142)
          - April 1865-May 1869, 1 volumes (Box 142)
          - January 1, 1862-May 8, 1869 (Box 60, Reel 67)
        - Executive Committee
          - August 1855-December 1868, 1 volumes (Box 142)
          - January 1862-April 1867, 1 volumes (Box 142)
          - July 1867-April 1869, 1 volumes (Box 142)
      - Mortgages and Related Material, 1855; 1857; 1885-1929 (scattered) (Box 142)
    - Michigan Southern Railroad Company
      - Act Authorizing Incorporation copied 1957, undated (Box 143)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors
          - July 1846-November 1850, 1 volumes (Box 143)
          - July 1846-April 1855, 1 volumes (Box 143)
          - January 8, 1846-April 25, 1855 (Box 60, Reel 67)
        - Finance Committee, 1849-1855; 1 volumes (Box 143)
    - Niagara Grand Island Bridge Company
      - Minutes: Shareholders Annual Meeting, 1913-1917; 1 volumes (Box 144)
    - Niagara Junction Railway Company
      - Board Dockets, 1966 (Box 144)
    - Niagara Peninsular Bridge Company
      - Minutes, November 1882-April 1883; 1 volumes (Box 144)
    - Niagara River Bridge Company
      - Board Dockets
        - 1922, 1934; 1938; 1944; 1949; 1952; 1954; 1955; 1957-1960 (Box 144)
        - 1961-1966 (Box 289)
    - Northern Central Michigan Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Correspondence (certified 1940), 1867-1883 (Box 144)
      - Minutes, 1866-1914; 1 volumes (Box 144)
      - Mortgage, 1873; 1907-1915 (scattered) (Box 144)
    - Northern Indiana and Chicago Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1850 (Box 144)
      - Minutes, September 1850-April 1855; 1 volumes (Box 144)
      - Minutes and Stock Ledger, September 1850-January 1852; 1 volumes (Box 144)
    - Northern Indiana Railroad Company (of Indiana)
      - Minutes
        - June 1851-February 1853, 1 volumes (Box 145)
        - June 1851-April 1855 (Box 145)
          (See: Buffalo and Mississippi Railroad Company, Minutes, 1835-1851.)
      - Mortgage and Related Correspondence, 1851; 1906 (Box 145)
    - Northern Indiana Railroad Company (of Indiana and Ohio)
      - Agreements of Consolidation and Merger, 1854-1855 (Box 145)
    - Northern Indiana Railroad Company (of Laporte County)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors, October 1849-April 1854; 1 volumes (Box 145)
        - Stockholders, June 1851-January 1853; 1 volumes (Box 145)
    - Northern Indiana Railroad Company (of Ohio)
      - Minutes, April 1851-June 1853; 1 volumes (Box 145)
    - Northwestern Ohio Railroad Company
      - Minutes, April-July 1871; 1 volumes (Box 146)
    - Ohio River and Lake Erie Railroad Company
      - Minutes, December 1897-February 1901; 1 volumes (Box 146)
    - Oil Creek Junction Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1870 (Box 146)
    - Oswego and Indiana Plank Road Company
      - Miscellaneous, 1849; 1857; 1902; 1919 (Box 146)
    - Rocky River Railroad Company
      - Minutes
        - February 1867-November 1880, 1 volumes (Box 146)
        - December 1880-May 1889, 1 volumes (Box 146)
    - Saginaw Bay and Northwestern Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association, 1876; 1879-1880 (Box 146)
      - Minutes, 1881-1893; 1 volumes (Box 146)
    - Saint Clair and Western Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Bylaws (certified 1919), 1906 (Box 147)
      - Board Docket, 1922; 1932; 1938; 1944; 1949 (Box 147)
      - Minutes, 1907-1949; 1 volumes (Box 147)
    - Saint Joseph, South Bend and Southern Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association and Dissolution, 1899; 1925; 1944-1945 (Box 147)
      - Board of Directors
        - Dockets, 1942-1944 (Box 147)
        - Minutes
          - 1899-November 4, 1942, 1 volumes (Box 147)
          - November 18, 1942-February 1945, 1 volumes (Box 147)
      - Cash Book, 1899-1942; 1 volumes (Box 148)
      - Interstate Commerce Commission Orders, 1942-1949 (Box 148)
      - Journal, General
        - 1899-1902 (Volume 50)
        - 1899-1949, 1 volumes (Box 148)
      - Ledger, General
        - 1899-1903 (Volume 51)
        - 1899-1949, 1 volumes (Box 148)
    - Saint Joseph Valley Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1925), 1869 (Box 149)
      - Minutes, March-October 1870; 1 volumes (Box 149)
    - Saint Louis, Sturgis and Battle Creek Railroad Company
      - Deed of Sale and Corporate History, 1889; 1953 (Box 149)
    - Schoolcraft and Three River Railroad Company
      - Minutes, 1855-1869 (Box 149)
    - Shenango Valley Railroad Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1912), 1886 (Box 149)
      - Board Docket, 1918; 1934; 1942-1959 (scattered) (Box 149)
      - Minutes
        - Board of Directors and Stockholders
          - 1886-1927 (Box 149)
          - 1928-1963 (Box 290)
        - Stockholders' Annual Meetings
          - 1910-1911, 1916-1960; 6 folders (Box 149)
          - 1961-1963 (Box 290)
    - Silver Creek and Dunkirk Railway Company
      - Articles of Association (certified 1913), 1890 (Box 150)
      - Minutes, 1890-1894; 1 volumes (Box 150)